Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), New York Local Records WAG.282
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Administrative Files
  This series is comprised of the administrative files of the union including correspondence of its executives, officers, and legal representatives. Correspondence from Kenneth Groot and Irving Lewis are particularly well represented. The union's efforts on behalf of its members of color, as well as other disenfranchised members are highlighted through the work of the union's committees and the Equal Opportunity Commission. In order to keep all of the staff involved with the union's daily activities, Read Files (referred to as "Blues" in the National office) consisting of each department's daily correspondence were circulated throughout the office. This series also includes handbooks, financial statements, files on the union's pension and health programs, correspondence concerning the publication of Stand By!, files on the local union's elections (including petitions, ballots, results, and press releases), and Non-Communist Affidavits, required for all officers and board members.
  - Actor's Fund: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1972-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Actor's Fund: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983-1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO: Correspondence and Related Materials Regarding Lie Detectors, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO: Correspondence and Related Materials Regarding the New York City Central Labor Council, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO: New York State Convention, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO: New York State Cope, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - AFRA Bulletins, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - AFTRA Broadcasting and Recording Industry Council on Alcoholism, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - AFTRA's New Green Room, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - AFTRA News Department, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Agency: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Agency: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Agency: Louis Shurr Agency, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Agency: Mort Schwartz Agency, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Antler, Helayne: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Antler, Helayne: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Antler, Helayne: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Artists' Directory, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Awards: Daytime Emmys, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Awards: Emmy Nominations, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Board: Availability of Board Minutes Resolution, 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Board: Blacklisting Resolution, 1953-1957 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Board: Collyer-Arthur Resolution, 1944-1946 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Board: Conflict of Interest, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Board: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Board: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1946-1959 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Board: Legal Council Resolution, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Board: Membership Ratification Resolution, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Board: Negro Employment Resolution, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Board: Resolutions, 1945-1951 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Board: Resolutions, 1952-1954 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Board: Resolutions, 1957-1963 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Board: Resolutions, 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Board: Resolutions, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Board: Seymour Collyer Resolution, 1947-1948 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Board: UHF and VHF Stations Resolution, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Brown, Pat: Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Casting Seminar Committee: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Central Labor Rehabilitation Council of New York, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Central Labor Rehabilitation Council of New York, 1979-1985 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Central Labor Rehabilitation Council of New York, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Committee: 45th Anniversary, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Commercial Workshop: Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Commercial Workshop: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1974-1980 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Commercial Workshop: Registration, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Commercial Workshop: Scripts, 1971-1982 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Committee: Access to Casting, 1982-1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Committee: AFTRA - Industry, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Committee: AFTRA-SAG on Non-Signatories, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Committee: AFTRA-SAG Wages and Working Conditions, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Committee: Agenda, 1978-1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Committee: Anti-Separatism Within AFTRA, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Committee: Awards, 1983-1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Committee: Broadcast, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Committee: Casting Seminar Explorations, 1977-1986 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Committee: Celebrations, 50th Anniversary Gala, 1983-1988 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Committee: Celebrations, Lists, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Committee: Celebrations, Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Committee: Celebrities to Visit St. Albans Hospital, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Committee: Commercial Workshop, 1972-1982 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Committee: Committees, General, 1978-1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Committee: Community Service, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Committee: Community Service, 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Committee: Convention Procedures, 1979-1987 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Committee: Cooperative Services, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Committee: CPR Training - Health and Fitness, 1982-1987 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Committee: Daytime Drama, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Committee: Executive, 1978-1987 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Committee: Executive and Finance, 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Committee: Fact Finding; Member Unions, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Committee: For Disabled Performers, Press, 1980-1984 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Committee: For Disabled Performers, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Committee: For Disabled Performers, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Committee: For Disabled Performers, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Committee: Fourteen, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Committee: Fund-Raising, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Committee: Insurance, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Committee: Interchangeability, 1982-1987 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Committee: Joint Management - Labor, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Committee: Joint Management - Labor, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Committee: Legislative and Resolutions, 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Committee[s]: Lists, 1967-1983 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Committee[s]: Lists, 1984-1988 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Committee: Membership Activities, 1980-1987 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Committee: Memorial Foundation, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Committee: Minors, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Committee: Negotiations, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Committee: Newsperson's Workshop, 1969-1980 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Committee: Newsperson's Workshop, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Committee: Nominating Convention Delegates, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Committee: Open Door, 1976-1983 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Committee: Open Door, 1984-1988 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Committee: Paymaster, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Committee: Paymaster, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Committee: Presidents, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Committee: Protest N.E.A. Cuts (Ad Hoc), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Committee: Public Access Cable, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Committee: Senior Performers, 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Committee: Servicemen, 1968-1980 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Committee: Singers' Wages and Working Conditions, 1961-1965 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Committee: Stand By! Editorial Board, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Committee: Stanley Green Audio-Video Center, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Committee: Stanley Green Audio-Video Center, 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Committee: Stanley Green Audio-Video Center, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Committee: Steering, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Committee: Strike, 1979-1987 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Committee: Strike Fund, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Committee: Strike Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Committee: Tenure, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Committee: Third Thursday Subcommittee, 1975-1984 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Committee: Tur/Transcription Codes, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Committee: Wages and Working Conditions, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Committee: Women's, Newsperson Questionnaires, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Committee: Women's, Correspondence and Related Material, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Committee: Women's, Reports, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Committee: WNYC Workshop Subcommittee, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Conaway, Donald: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Conaway, Donald: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Constitution: Constitutional Amendments, 1942-1953 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Constitution: Constitutional Amendments, 1958-1962 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Constitution: Constitutional Changes, 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Constitution: Constitutional Amendments, 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Constitution: Constitutional Committee, 1935-1938 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Constitution: Constitutional Committee, 1953-1958 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Constitution: Constitutional Committee, 1978-1986 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Constitution: Constitutional Review Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Academy of Humor, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Actors and Producers, Re: Sound Recordings, 1977-1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Agents and Producers, Re: Sound Recordings, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Agents and Producers, Re: Sound Recordings, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Agents and Producers, Re: Sound Recordings, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Career Academy, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Cheng, Stephen, Re: "Oriental" Members, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Dick Moore Associates, 1976-1981 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: General, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: General, Jan-Jun 1965 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: General, Jul-Dec 1965 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: General, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: General, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: General, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: General, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: General, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: General, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: New York State, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Patco, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Piracy, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Puppeteers, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: U.S. Government, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: U.S. Government, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: U.S. Government, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Council of Motion Pictures and Television Unions, 1975-1985 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Credit Union: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Credit Union: Handwritten Notes, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Credit Union: Printed Materials, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Credit Union: Press Clips, 1962-1966 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Dallas-Fort Worth Local: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Department of Professional Employees: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Dowell, Reginald: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Dowell, Reginald: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Dowell, Reginald: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Dowell, Reginald: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Dowell, Reginald: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Dowell, Reginald: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-Apr 1984 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Dowell, Reginald: Correspondence and Related Materials, May-Dec 1984 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Dowell, Reginald: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Elections: Local Board, Results, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results of Board Replacements, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petition, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Elections: Local Board, Vacancies, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Elections: Local Board, Local Elections, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Elections: Local Board, Nomination Petitions, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Elections: Local Board, Ballots and Results, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Elections: National Board, Nomination Petitions, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Elections: National Board, Nomination Petitions, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Elections: National Board, Nomination Petitions, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Elections: National Board, Nomination Petitions, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Elections: National Board, Nomination Petitions, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Elections: National Board, Nomination Petitions, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Elections: National Board, Ballots and Results, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Committee, 1969-1988 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1969-1976 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977-1979 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Members, 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: National Division Lists, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Press Clippings, 1976-1983 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Press Clippings, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Pride [Racial] Kits, 1980-1985 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Questionnaires, 1982-1987 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports, Cincinnati Local, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports for "All My Children", 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports for "Another World", 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports for "As the World Turns", 1983-1985 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports for "The Edge of Night", 1983 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports for "Guiding Light", 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports for "Loving", 1983-1987 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports for "One Life to Live", 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports for "Ryan's Hope", 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports for "Search for Tomorrow", 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports, General, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports, SAG Los Angeles, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Reports, Soap Auditions, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Union Publications, 1970-1982 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Exclusive Agency Contract: Samples, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Publications, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Financial Statements, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Financial Statements, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Financial Statements, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Financial Statements, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Financial Statements, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Financial Statements, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Financial Statements, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Financial Statements, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Financial Statements, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Financial Statements, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Financial Statements, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Financial Statements, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Financial Statements, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Financial Statements, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Financial Statements, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Financial Statements, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Financial Statements, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Financial Statements, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Financial Statements, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Financial Statements, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Financial Statements, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - General, 1945-1959 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - General, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - General, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - General, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - General, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - General, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - General, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - General, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - General, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - General, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - General, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - General, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - General, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1958-1965 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)